Sandro Fernandes UI & UX Designer

Experience

Feb. 2019 - Present

UI & UX Designer

Critical TechWorks - BMW Group

Apr 2014 - Feb 2019

Digital Designer

Instituto Superior Técnico, University of Lisbon

2010-2014

Digital Content Manager

Cienciapt.net

2011

Intern Designer

City Hall of Cartaxo

Education

2012-2015

Master in New Media and Web Practices

NOVA School of Social Sciences and Humanities, Universidade NOVA de Lisboa

2008-201

Bachelor in Multimedia Communication and Education

School of Education,

Polytechnic Institute of Santarém

Skills

Design



Sketch



in Invision

Front-end





SASS / SCSS

JS (basics)

Profile

Short story

I'm a simple person who loves simple things.

Long short story

I was born in Lisbon, Portugal, but moved right away to the middle of the country - near the beautiful Serra da Estrela - then to Cartaxo where I spent most of my childhood. Now I'm back in Lisbon again.

I'm left handed and always liked to draw.

I'm currently working at Critical TechWorks, supporting the design of the next generation of software systems for the BMW Group's future driving machines.

I tend to describe myself as an User Interface designer, User Experience thinker, and a Front-end enthusiast.

Interest

Life

🌿 Nature

🧡 Family

Sports

Worl

User Experience

User Interfaces

Usability

Accessibility